Technology is never a neutral tool for achieving human ends.
技术从来都不是实现人类目的的中立工具。
Technological innovations reshape people as they use these innovations to control their environment.
人们利用技术创新来掌控自己所处的环境，与此同时，这些创新也在重塑人本身。
Artificial intelligence, for example, is altering humanity.
例如，人工智能正在改变人类。
While the term AI conjures up anxieties about killer robots or catastrophic levels of unemployment, there are other, deeper implications.
虽然“人工智能”一词会勾起人们对杀手机器人或失业达到灾难性程度的焦虑，但人工智能还有其他更深层的影响。
As AI increasingly shapes the human experience, how does this change what it means to be human?
随着人工智能日益塑造人类的体验，这会如何改变身为人类的意义？
Central to the problem is a person’s capacity to make choices, particularly judgments that have moral implications.
问题的核心在于人做选择的能力，尤其是做出具有道德含义的判断的能力。
Aristotle argued that the capacity for making practical judgments depends on regularly making them—on habit and practice.
亚里士多德主张，做出实践判断的能力有赖于经常做这种判断，也就是有赖于习惯和练习。
We see the emergence of machines as substitute judges in a variety of everyday contexts as a potential threat to people learning how to effectively exercise judgment themselves.
机器以代人做判断的角色出现在各种日常情境中，我们认为，这对人们学习如何自己有效地运用判断力构成了潜在威胁。
In the workplace, managers routinely make decisions about who to hire or fire and which loan to approve, to name a few.
在职场上，管理者经常要决定雇用谁、解雇谁、批准哪笔贷款，这里仅举几例。
These are areas where algorithmic prescription is replacing human judgment, and so people who might have had the chance to develop practical judgment in these areas no longer will.
在这些领域，算法给出的指令正在取代人的判断，因此，那些本可能有机会在这些领域培养实践判断力的人，将再也没有这样的机会了。
Recommendation engines, which are increasingly prevalent intermediaries in people’s consumption of culture, may serve to constrain choice and minimize luck.
推荐引擎日益普遍地充当人们文化消费的中介，它们可能会起到限制选择、把运气成分降到最低的作用。
By presenting consumers with algorithmically selected choices of what to watch, read, stream and visit next, companies are replacing human taste with machine taste.
企业向消费者呈现由算法挑选出的选项，供他们从中选择接下来看什么、读什么、在线播放什么、访问什么，这样一来，企业就是在用机器的品味取代人的品味。
In one sense, this is helpful.
从某种意义上说，这是有益的。
After all, machines can survey a wider range of choices than any individual is likely to have the time or energy to do on their own.
毕竟，机器能够审视的选项范围更广，任何个人都不太可能有足够的时间或精力独自做到这一点。
At the same time, though, this selection is optimizing for what people are likely to prefer based on what they’ve preferred in the past.
但与此同时，这种挑选依据的是人们过去的偏好，以他们可能偏爱的东西为优化目标。
We think there is some risk that people’s options will be constrained by their past in a new and unanticipated way.
我们认为存在一定风险：人们的选择会以一种新的、意想不到的方式受到自己过去的限制。
As machine learning algorithms improve and as they train on more extensive data sets, larger parts of everyday life are likely to become utterly predictable.
随着机器学习算法不断改进，并在规模更大的数据集上接受训练，更大一部分日常生活很可能会变得完全可以预测。
The predictions are going to get better and better, and they will ultimately make common experiences more efficient and pleasant.
预测会越来越精准，最终会让平常的种种体验变得更高效、更愉快。
Algorithms could soon—if they don’t already—have a better idea about which show you’d like to watch next and which job candidate you should hire than you do.
算法可能很快就会比你更清楚你接下来想看哪个节目、应该雇用哪位求职者——如果它们现在还没有做到的话。
One day, humans may even find a way for machines to make these decisions without some of the biases that humans typically display.
有朝一日，人类甚至可能会找到办法，让机器在做这些决定时，不带有人类通常会表现出的某些偏见。
But to the extent that unpredictability is part of how people understand themselves and part of what people like about themselves, humanity is in the process of losing something significant.
但是，如果说不可预测性是人们认识自我的一部分，也是人们喜欢自己的地方之一，那么就此而言，人类正在失去某种重要的东西。
As they become more and more predictable, the creatures inhabiting the increasingly AI-mediated world will become less and less like us.
这个世界日益以人工智能为中介，栖居其中的生物随着自身越来越可预测，将会变得越来越不像我们。